# **Brian Connors**

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



# **Work History**

# GROUP PROJECTS SAN DIEGO JS MEETUP PIPELINE

This project was a four man team where we created a utility app for the admins of the SDJS meetup group. This app allows speakers to register to speak at any up coming event and allows the admin to easily manage each event. My main role on the team was first scaffolding out the base app in react and redux, and then creating automated emails that got sent to the speaker and admin when someone registered.

GITHUB: https://github.com/OriginCodeAcademy/sdjs-speaker-pipeline

#### **SPACE BOX**

This project was an 8 man group where we built a jukebox app that allows people to submit songs from spotify from their own computer onto the hosts spotify account. It started off as a mob activity that various students made while in class each week. For our final project we were tasked with adding more features to the base app. My main role was to refactor the base code from one component into multiple smaller components and set up the store with redux.

GITHUB:

https://github.com/OriginCodeAcademy/spacebox

#### **BULLS EYE PEST CONTROL**

2014-2018

Pest Control Technician 2014-2018

With this job I mainly worked alone as I spent the entire day driving from home to home treating our customers homes with their various pest problems. This taught me the value of time management as I had a set list of services to complete each day without any management supervision.

#### HOMEFRONT PEST CONTROL

2012-20014

pest control technician

Same overall job description and experience as Bulls Eye

#### **ALBERTSONS**

2007-2012

courtesy clerk/ cashier/ service deli tech/ night crew stocker/ produce clerk/ dairy clerk Over the course of my employment here I worked in various departments. Most of them involved stocking shelves efficiently while still greeting customers and providing excellent customer service in a timely, friendly manner.

# Personal Profile

I have worked in the retail and pest control industry for a combined 11 years now. With those careers I have developed customer service and time management skills to complete projects on time. However, neither of these careers were satisfactory to me. With that being said, I look forward to a career in computer programming.

# **Contact Details**

**Brian Connors** 

31011 Jedediah Smith Rd Temecula, CA. 92592

EMAIL: seahorse8789@gmail.com

**PHONE:** 951 240 0056

**GITHUB**: https://github.com/BladeSe7en **LINKEDIN**: linkedin.com/in/brian-connors-

081a3a171

PORTFOLIO: https://brian-connors-

portfolio.herokuapp.com/

## **Education**

Temecula Valley High School 2004-2008

Diploma

Origin Coding Academy certificate of completion

2018

## **Notable Skills**

-JavaScript/ES6 -MongoDB -React -mySQL

-React Redux -CSS/LESS/SASS/HTML

-React Router -bootstrap

eact Router -bootstrap

-Express -GIT -Node.js -Jira

-loopback -JQuery